{
    "subject": "resource/Oando",
    "predicate": "ontology/product",
    "object": "resource/Petrochemical",
    "human_readable": "Oando produces Petrochemical.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9247519373893738,
            "question": "Is Petrochemical a product of Oando?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.880534827709198,
            "question": "Does Oando manufacture anything besides Petrochemical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8389242887496948,
            "question": "Who are the customers of Oando's Petrochemical products?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7276699542999268,
            "question": "What does Oando produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.510224461555481,
            "question": "Name some products made by Oando."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46735015511512756,
            "question": "What industry is Oando involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34856340289115906,
            "question": "What are the applications of Petrochemical products?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3345249593257904,
            "question": "What kind of company is Oando?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2060256451368332,
            "question": "Where is Oando located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19171491265296936,
            "question": "What is the importance of Petrochemical in the global market?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Oando produces Petrochemical.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5942_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Oando located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5942_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of company is Oando?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5942_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the applications of Petrochemical products?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5942_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5942_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Oando Trading's key trading commodities include petrochemicals, industrial & liquefied natural gas, refined oil products and crude oil. This information supports the triple \"Oando produces Petrochemical\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions that Oando Trading, a subsidiary of the Oando Group, is a leading supplier of petroleum products in Nigeria. Its key trading commodities include petrochemicals, among others. This supports the statement that Oando produces Petrochemical."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}